Mohamed Rabie Rabie Elmdary

4st Algalban, Algharbia, Egypt.

+20 1282859139

engm5081@gmail.com

https://github.com/MohamedElmdary

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-elmdary-949968181

Objective

Seeking an opportunity to participate in collaborating, competitive and creative environment where I can use my background within software design and development, and also develop my potential in business development

Skills Summary

Senior front end developer with experience and good knowledge in html5, css3, js, react, angular, vue, graphql, state managements, bootstrap and material design, apollo-client. In back end development Field I have experience in nodejs, ssr, expressjs, nestjs, mongo db, mysql, graphql, prisma, apollo-server and graphql-yoga.

In testing I have a little experience with jest and mocha.

Skilled at learning new concepts and techniques, working well under pressure and communicating ideas clearly and effectively.

Work Experiences

Company: Envato Market

[7/2017 - 7/2018]

Position Held: Front End Developer

Accomplishments: creating static websites that allow users to show contents for advertisements or showing personal information.

Company: Techs On Upwork

[9/2018 - 2/2019]

Position Held: Senior Front End Developer

Accomplishments: work on a dashboard that allow to observe users and there transactions in a market system using reactjs.

Company: Io-tech

[5/2019 - 4/2020]

Position Held: Senior Front End Developer

Accomplishments: creating a dashboard using angular and material angular to show real time values and communicate with SCADA system via some low level protocols using angular and graphql.

Projects

Project Name: My Portfolio

Description: A website that allow my to show my projects and the current skills and my

experience and public speaks.

Tools: angular, material angular, angular universal (ssr), expressjs.

Link: https://elmdary-cv.herokuapp.com/

Project Name: Life Achievements

Description: A Project that allow users to tracks there a achievements by losing a bad habit or

start some good habits.

Tools: nodejs, graphql, graphql-yoga, prisma. **Link**: https://protected-basin-72892.herokuapp.com/

Note: the front end for this project was written in java for a native android application.

Project Name: Mern Blog

Description: A blog like site allow users to post and others react to it and share if needed and

you can follow other users and vice vers. **Tools**: react, nodejs, expressjs, mongo db . **Link**: https://react-socialapp.herokuapp.com/

Operating System

I have been working with linux for over 1.5 years.

Education

CSED – 2016-2021

A student in Mansoura university, Studing computer science and embedded systems in faculty of engineering .

Languages

Arabic: mother tongue.

English: very good at listen – good in talk.

Personal Information

Date of birth: 14/12/1997. Nationality: Egyptian.

Military status: I have no military because I don't have any brother.

Marital Status: Single.

https://elmdary-cv.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/MohamedElmdary

https://themeforest.net/user/mohamedelmdary

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-elmdary-949968181

https://codepen.io/mohamed9714